Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Communication - Habel quits bargaining committee - sell-out to Hoffa revealed, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: CWA's Participation in International Affairs, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Defense fund rules, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Local defense fund ground rules, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Nobody's mad at anybody!, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Simple as ABC, Publication (Box 148, Folder 7)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: an invitation to join CWA, the union for communications employees, Publication (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Internal organizing: a guide for the locals of the Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Keys to successful organizing: planning an effective campaign: a guide for the locals of the Communication Workers of America, 1960; Publication (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Meet your CWA Representative, Publication (Box 148, Folder 8)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A proposed ACA Policy and program for vets, Publication (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Press releases, 1955-1956 (Box 148, Folder 9)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Resolutions, 30th Annual Convention, Communications Workers of America, Sheraton-Park Hotel, Washington, D.C., June 17-21, 1968, Publication (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Resolutions, ACA 10th Biennial Convention, Nov. 2, 3, 4, 1950, Publication (Box 148, Folder 10)
    Author: American Communications Association
  - Item 3: Resolutions, Eighth Annual Convention, Communications Workers of America, affiliated with CIO-CCL, Cleveland, Ohio, June 21-25, 1954, Publication (Box 148, Folder 10)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Administrative structure National Bargaining Units, Eighth Annual Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
    Notes: Communications Workers of America affiliated with CIO-CCL, Cleveland, Ohio, June 21-25, 1954
  - Item 2: Correspondence to All Divisions: Attention Presidents, Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Report and recommendations of the Joint Committee for uniting CWA-CIO and TWOC-CIO, Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Report of the Constitution Committee to the Eighth Annual CWA Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Report of the rules committee to the eighth annual CWA convention, 1954; Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Report of the Secretary-Treasurer of the Eighth Annual CWA Convention, 1954; Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Statement of domestic economic policy, 1954; Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Statement on foreign policy / Communications Workers of America affiliated with CIO-CCL, Cleveland, Ohio, June 21-25, 1954, Publication (Box 148, Folder 11)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Handbook consolidating and simplifying rules governing the Administration of the CWA Defense Fund, 1954; Publication (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Structure (chart) of Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 149, Folder 1)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: What do you knowabout the Communications Workers of America, 1953; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: 1949 Wage increases, Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
    Notes: R&S Releases
  - Item 3: Bell System pension data, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Rate increases in the Bell System, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Wage rates in Independent Telephone companies, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: 1952-53 Public Utility Industry, 1952-1953 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    Notes: Agreements providing for partial or complete company-paid-for hospital and surgical insurance
  - Item 7: An invitation to join CWA, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: An invitation to join CWA, 1953; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Charts - Bell System Vacation policy, 1938; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Charts - Selected non-contributory pension plans in New York State, 1958; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Comparison of earnings between nonsupervisory workers of Bell System Operating Companies, 1955; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Comparison of four selected telephone industry pension plans, 1954; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: CWA-CIO Research Dept.: Memo to Mr. Curtis Fletcher, 1953; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
    Notes: Subject: contract Gains - Independent Telephone Companies
  - Item 14: Facts and figures about the telephone industry, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
    Author: Communications Workers of America. Research and Statistics Dept.
  - Item 15: Membership of CWA by regions, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Minimum and maximum wage rates for operators in independent telephone companies in United States with which CWA holds contracts, 1955; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: National Emergency disputes in 1948, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Termination dates of CWA contracts - Bell System, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: What do you knowabout the Communications Workers of America, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 2)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bell System Directors and the positions they hold simultaneously..., 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Bell System pension data, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Bell System profits - 1948, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Consumers' Price Index, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Depreciation reserves - Bell System, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Effects of contemplated dial conversion program, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Rate increases in the Telephone Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Wage rates in independent telephone companies, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Working women's budgets in twelve states, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: 1949 Wage rates in Western Electric Plants, Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: State and Federal telephone regulatory bodies, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: State voting laws summarized, 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Wage increases - Independent Telephone Companies, 1949; Publication (Box 149, Folder 3)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Let's hold a good union meeting, Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: A primer on persuasion, Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
    Author: Communications Workers of America. Training Dept.
  - Item 3: C.W.A. study primer on economics, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Communications dynamics, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Concepts of leadership, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: CWA steward's manual: a guide to leadership., Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: CWA training program: conducting departmental meetings, 1975; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: CWA training program: CWA structure and policy, 1975; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Fund raising for CWA locals, 1975; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Institutional racism & sexism conflict resolution for CWA leadership, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Labor and the American legal system, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Organizing and persuasion: Instructor's manual, NE 1733, 1975; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Organizing techniques: Instructor's manual, NE-1637, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Principles and purposes of CWA, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Problem solving for labor activists, 1974; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Using media, 1975; Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: What, where, how for local officers: an operating guide, Publication (Box 149, Folder 4)
- Unionwise, Publication (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Unionwise - (newspaper), 1958; Publication (Box 149, Folder 5)
    Notes: Oct., Dec.
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Outline of ACA history, Publication (Box 149, Folder 6)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ACA Award, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: American Communications Assoc., CIO and Press Wireless, Inc., 1935; Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
    Notes: Arbitration case
  - Item 3: Before the National War Labor Board: a summary of the wage case, 1942; Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
    Notes: Presented by the American Communications Association affiliated with the CIO, on behalf of the employees of Postal Telegraph and Cable Company
  - Item 4: Comm. For Co. and Agents, Atlantic and Gulf Coasts, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Western Union Telegraph Company, 1948; Publication (Box 149, Folder 7)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Calling all ACA Members: Seven reasons why you can't vote for Joseph P. Selly, hopeless bungler, Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Committee of One Thousand to re-elect Joseph P. Selly, President of ACA-CIO, Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
    Notes: Election flyer
  - Item 3: For Marine Dep't., Vice-President, ACA-CIO, Jack Winocur, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: For Secretary-Treasurer of ACA-CIO we need ---., Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Now's your chance to vote for Jobs- and job security, Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Official ballot, 1944; Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Official ballot, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: These are our candidates - To maintain a united, strong, fighting ACA-CIO, Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Vote for Wayne P. Paschal, Secretary-Treasurer, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: We need Joseph P. Selly as President of ACA-CIO, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Ballots for election of Delegates to 8th National Convention, National marice Department Conference and on proposition submitted by the Atlantic District Executive Committee, Publication (Box 149, Folder 8)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Church and labor, Publication (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Correspondence - to All Members of Atlantic District Marine Dept., 1944; Publication (Box 149, Folder 9)
    Notes: Subject: General Referendum
  - Item 3: Minutes from the regular meeting, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 9)
    Author: Atlantic District Executive Committee
    Notes: 2nd, 3rd, Special
  - Item 4: Union News Broadcasts, Publication (Box 149, Folder 9)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Local 40 News (newsletter), 1947; Publication (Box 149, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.1:no.7-12
  - Item 2: Local 40 News (newsletter), 1948; Publication (Box 149, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-11
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report to the International Convention, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 11)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Challenge (newsletter), 1951; Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Challenge (newsletter), 1948; Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Employee's 1955 income tax handbook, Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Financial report, 1947; Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District
  - Item 5: Information Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Local 40 News (newsletter), 1947; Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
    Notes: v. II, no. 3 (1947)
  - Item 7: Membership Book (Women's Auxiliary), Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: N.F.T.W. Exposed!, Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: This is what I am voting for, Publication (Box 149, Folder 12)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: An unprecedented moveasks the war shipping administration to extend wage increases., 1945; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Chart of Maritime War Emergency Board Order on Voyage & Area Bonuses, Effective July 15, 1945, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Correspondence - 'Dear Brothers', 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Correspondence - To: ACA Marine Dept. Administrative Committee, 1944; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Improved working conditions for ACA Radio Officers, 1945; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Information for Gallup's Island graduates, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Marine Report, 1946; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
    Notes: Oct.-Dec. 1946
  - Item 8: Marine Report, 1947; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
    Notes: Jan. 1947
  - Item 9: MSG, 1944; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
    Notes: 1944 May
  - Item 10: Permit card rules, 1943; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Statement on Commission for Merchant Marine Radio Officers, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Stop and think and brother!, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: The C.I.O. program-for-a-better-U.S.A., 1945; Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: The only Nation-wide Union for Marine Radio Officers, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Urgent-to All Members, Publication (Box 149, Folder 13)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Canadian Section Report to ACA Convention, April 8, 1946, Publication (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the regular meeting (Sept. 11, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Communications Association, Pacific District, Canadian Section Local #4, Marine Dept.
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 20th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 10, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: 22nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 24, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 15th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (July 2, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: 8th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (April 23, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 2)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District - Port of Baltimore
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 13th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (April 30, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District - Port of Boston
  - Item 2: 14th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 7, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: 15th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 14, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: 18th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 4, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: 19th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 11, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: 24th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (July 23, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: 25th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (July 30, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: 26th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 6, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: 29th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 3, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: 30th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 10, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: 31st Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 24, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Special Meeting Minutes (Sept. 16, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 3)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 9th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 4, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Special Membership Meeting Minutes (June 28, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 12th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 18, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 4)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District - Port of New Orleans
  - Item 4: 8th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Feb. 24, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 4)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 12th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 25, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: 13th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 27, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 14th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (April 2, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: 17th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Apr. 24, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: 18th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 1, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: 20th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 14, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: 23rd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 10, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: 24th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 12, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: 26th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 1, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: 27th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 8, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: 28th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 15, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: 30th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Dec. 28, 1943), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: 32nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 7, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: 34th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 21, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: 36th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 4, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: 40th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Nov. 7, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: 44th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Dec. 5, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: 44th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 30, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: 45th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Nov. 6, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: 46th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Nov. 13, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: 6th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Feb. 6, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: 7th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Feb. 18, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: 9th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 4, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: 18th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 23, 1944), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District - Marine Dept.
  - Item 25: 22nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 20, 1942), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlanta District
    Notes: Held at Headquarters
  - Item 26: 23rd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 27, 1942), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: 24th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (July 18, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: 46th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Nov. 19, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
    Author: American Communications Association - Atlantic District - Port of New York
  - Item 29: 49th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Dec. 10, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 5)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 15th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Apr. 16, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: 18th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 7, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: 19th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 14, 1945), 1946; Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: 20th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 21, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: 21st Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (May 28, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: 22nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 2, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: 23rd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (June 11, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: 10th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 12, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: 12th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Mar. 26, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: 13th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Apr. 2, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: 14th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Apr. 9, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: 32nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 13, 1945), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: 33rd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (July 9, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: 34th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Aug. 27, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: 35th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 3, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: 38th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 10, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: 39th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 1, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: 40th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 8, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: 42nd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 22, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: 43rd Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Oct. 29, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: 44th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Nov. 5, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: 4th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Jan. 28, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: 51st Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Dec. 24, 1948), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: 8th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Feb. 26, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Special Meeting Minutes (Aug. 3, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: Special Meeting Minutes (June 15, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: 37th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 17, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: 38th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Sept. 24, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: 5th Regular Membership Meeting Minutes (Feb. 4, 1947), Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: District President's Report, 1946; Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Item 31: The role of the ROU-CTU in the Maritime Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 150, Folder 6)
- ACA (American Communications Association), Publication (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Regular Membership Mtg., San Francisco 390th (Apr. 3, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Regular Membership Mtg., San Francisco 391st (Apr. 10, 1946), Publication (Box 150, Folder 7)